bhs.co.uk 2013-10-16

# Privacy Policy - BHS

Bhs Limited (we and us) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This policy (together with our website terms & conditions) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998, the data controller is Bhs Limited.

We may collect and process the following data about you: Details of transactions you carry out through our website www.bhs.co.uk (the Site) and of the fulfilment of your orders; information that you provide by filling in forms on the Site, including, but not limited to, information provided at the time of requesting or subscribing to any service, uploading material or becoming a registered user or if you enter any competition or promotion sponsored by us; information from surveys that we use for research purposes, if you choose to respond to them; communications you send to us, for example to report a problem with or submit a comment regarding the Site; and details of your visits to the Site, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data and the resources that you access.

This website uses cookies to collect information. 

**What is a cookie?  
**Cookies are small files of letters and numbers that are downloaded onto your computer or mobile or other handheld device when you access certain websites.  Cookies allow a website to recognise a user’s device and help your browser navigate through the website by allowing you to log in automatically or remembering settings you selected during earlier visits (among other functions).  Cookies do not harm your computer.  If you would like to learn more about cookies in general you can visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

**Use of cookies on this website  
**Cookies help us to provide you with a good experience when you browse this website and allow you to make full use of the online shopping and personalised features available on this website.  We do not use cookies to collect or record information such as your name, address or payment details.

We use cookies on this website for the following main purposes:  
• for technical purposes essential for the operation of this website, such as keeping track of your current shopping session and enabling you to proceed to checkout and pay for products;  
• to distinguish you from other users of this website, so we can personalise your shopping experience by making this website and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests and so we can remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the country you are in) when you return to visit this website;  
• to collect statistical information about how visitors use this website, so we can improve the way this website works and measure the success of competitions and campaigns; and  
• to enable us to fulfil our contractual obligations to third parties, for example to pay a partner if you have made a purchase on this website by following a link from their website. 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies.  Unless you have adjusted your browser settings so that it will refuse cookies, cookies will be set when you access this website.  By using and browsing this website, you consent to cookies being used in accordance with this Cookie Policy.  If you do not consent, you must either disable cookies or refrain from using this website.  Please scroll down to the 'how to manage cookies' section ** ** for information on how to manage and disable cookies.

**Our Cookies  
**Below is a list of the main cookies that are set by us when you access this website and a description of what we use them for:

  **Flash cookies  
** We may display video content on BHS.co.uk using Adobe Flash Player.  Adobe uses Flash cookies to improve your experience as a user.  If you wish to disable or delete a Flash cookie, please visit Adobe Flashplayer Security Settings.  Please bear in mind that if you disable Flash cookies you will be unable to access certain content on our website which uses Adobe Flash Player, such as videos.

**Third party cookies  
**Some cookies may be set by third parties when you visit this website.  These third parties may be suppliers who partner with us to deliver our website, companies that participate with us in affiliate marketing programmes and other third parties.  These cookies are controlled by the third parties, so please check the third-party websites for more information about these cookies and how to manage them.   These third party cookies do not collect personal data from which the third party would be able to identify individual customers.

Some of our third party partners that may set cookies on this website include:

**Social buttons  
**If you 'share' BHS.co.uk content with friends through social networks – such as Facebook, Google and Twitter - you may be sent cookies from these third party websites. We don't control the setting of these cookies, so we suggest you check the third-party websites for more information about their cookies and how to manage them.

**Flash cookies  
** We may display video content on BHS.co.uk using Adobe Flash Player.  Adobe uses Flash cookies to improve your experience as a user.  If you wish to disable or delete a Flash cookie, please visit Adobe Flashplayer Security Settings.  Please bear in mind that if you disable Flash cookies you will be unable to access certain content on our website which uses Adobe Flash Player, such as videos.

**How to Manage Cookies  
**You can enable or disable cookies by changing your website browser settings to accept or reject cookies as required.  How to do this will depend on the browser you use.  We have provided further information below on how to check which browser you use and how to manage cookies.  Please bear in mind that if cookies are not enabled on your computer, your activities will be restricted to browsing this website and you will not be able to add products to your shopping bag and buy them.

**Checking which browser you use  
**If you are using a PC - go to 'Help' and select the 'About' option  
If you are using a Mac - click on the Apple menu within the browser and select the 'About' option

Once you know which brower you are using, follow the instructions below to check if you have cookies enabled on your computer:

**Checking cookies - PCs  
**Microsoft Internet Explorer 6,7,8  
\- Go to 'Tools' at the top of your browser window. Select 'Internet options'. Click on the 'Privacy' tab  
\- Ensure that your Privacy level is set to Medium or below to enable cookies

Mozilla Firefox  
\- Go to 'Tools' and select Options  
\- Click the Privacy icon  
\- Click on Cookies and choose 'allow sites to set cookies'

Google Chrome  
\- Go to 'Tools' and select Options  
\- Click 'Under the Hood'  and select the 'Content settings' button within the 'Privacy' section  
\- Choose 'Allow local data to be set'

**Checking cookies – Macs  
**Safari on OSX  
\- Click 'Safari' and select 'Preferences'   
\- Click 'Security' then 'Accept cookies'

Mozilla and Netscape on OSX  
\- Click on 'Mozilla' or 'Netscape' and select 'Preferences'  
\- Find ‘Cookies’ under 'Privacy & Security'  
\- Select 'Enable cookies for the originating web site only'

Microsoft Internet Explorer on OSX  
\- Click 'Explorer' and select 'Preferences'  
\- Find 'Cookies' under ‘Receiving Files’  
\- Select 'Never Ask' 

Opera  
\- Click 'Menu' and select 'Settings'  
\- Select 'Preferences' and then 'Advanced'   
\- Select 'Accept cookies'

If you are not happy with the way that we use cookies then you should delete BHS cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, "Private Browsing" in Firefox and Safari etc.)

The data that we collect from you is processed by staff who work either for us or one of our group companies or for one of our service providers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. All payment transactions will be processed on our behalf by BIBIT Global Payment Services (a divisions of The Royal Bank of Scotland Group). This means that your credit/debit card details are provided directly to BIBIT and are never revealed to us. BIBIT operates a secure server to process your payment details. BIBIT encrypts your credit/debit card information and authorises payment. You can access BIBIT's privacy policy [here](http://www.bibit.com/content.php?page=privacy) to read more about BIBIT's security measures and how your personal information is processed. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain features or parts of the Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. You must not share the password with anyone. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

We use information held about you in the following ways: to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, for example to fulfil your orders; to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have indicated that you wish to be contacted for such purposes by post, email, SMS, telephone or other means of electronic communication; to ensure that content from the Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer; to allow you to participate in any interactive features of our services, when you choose to do so; and to notify you about changes to our services. We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about third party goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these, where you have indicated that you wish to be contacted for such purposes by post, email, SMS, telephone or other means of electronic communication. If you do not want us to use your data for direct marketing purposes, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please check or un-check (as directed) the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data.

We may disclose your personal information to any affiliated company within our group. We may disclose your personal information to third parties: in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets. If we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us about our customers will be one of the transferred assets. If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our website Terms & Conditions or other agreements; or to protect our rights, property, or safety or those of our customers or other third parties. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking or un-checking (as directed) certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data or by following the unsubscribe link on any marketing emails we send you. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at unsubscribe@bhs.co.uk or, if you have become a registered user, by logging into the Site and changing your marketing preferences through the 'My Account' option.

The Site may, from time to time, contain hyperlinks to and from internet sites operated by other organisations. If you follow a hyperlink to any of these sites, please note that they will have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to such sites.

The Data Protection Act 1998 gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with that Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee not exceeding £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.
